https://research.uci.edu/privacy-policy.html

Sign in to customize this list of links to match your every day usage.
Add This Page
to your personal toolbox for easy return access on any device by logging in with your UCInetID.
Save
Save this page to your personal toolbox.
×
News & Announcements| Contact Us | Applications & Forms
Menu
About the OfficeCenters & InstitutesConducting Research at UCI: Getting StartedElectronic Research Administration (ERA)Facilities & ServicesIntegrity in ResearchPolicy LibraryResearch DevelopmentResearch Engagement & FacilitationResearch ProtectionsSponsored ProjectsTraining & EducationUC Irvine Office of Research
About the OfficeSponsored ProjectsResearch ProtectionsResearch DevelopmentElectronic Research Administration (ERA)Research Engagement & FacilitationCenters & InstitutesFacilities & ServicesIntegrity in ResearchTraining & EducationPolicy Library
Menu
About the OfficeAdministration | Financial Operations | Research ProgramsOffice of Research Organizational ChartsOffice of Research Staff DirectoryOffice of the Vice Chancellor for ResearchRequests Handled by the Office of the VCRResearch AdministrationStats, Facts & FiguresCenters & InstitutesAll Centers and InstitutesCampus CentersOrganized Research UnitsOther Centers & InstitutesSchool CentersSpecial Research ProgramsElectronic Research Administration (ERA)Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)KR Tips from barbERAKuali Research (KR)KR Proposal DevelopmentNeed Help? Contact ERAUser SupportFacilities & Services
+
Shared FacilitiesShared Facilities by Sponsoring Unit
+
Transgenic Mouse FacilityContact UsFrequently Asked QuestionsNewsOnline ResourcesPrices - effective Oct 1, 2019ServicesBreedingCRISPR / Cas9 Mediated Genome Engineering ServicesDNA Microinjection ServicesEmbryo & Sperm Cryopreservation and Revival ServicesES Cell Injection ServicesGene TargetingGenotypingOther ServicesTargeted TransgenesisTechnical AdviceConstruct DesignDNA Preparation TechniquesTMF Tutorials
+
ULARAnimal PurchasingAnimal TransfersAnimal Welfare ConcernsContact ULARDrug DosagesSheepPolicies & InformationRecharge RatesTrainingULAR Facility AccessULAR FormsVeterinary ServicesIntegrity in ResearchResearch MisconductSponsor Requirements for RCR TrainingTraining in the Responsible Conduct of ResearchPolicy LibraryResearch DevelopmentFinding Funding OpportunitiesFind Your RDOFunding SourcesBridge FundingEquipment Funding Federal, Private, and Internal Funding Sources Limited Submission Grant OpportunitiesYoung Investigator Funding OpportunitiesTraining GrantsData TablesData RequestsDefinitionsGuidance + Tips & TrickseRA CommonsxTRACTxTrainPost AwardBudget CategoriesRebudgeting of FundsReporting & CloseoutProgram PlanReports & DataResearch Engagement & FacilitationCannabis ResearchConducting Hemp ResearchConducting Marijuana ResearchDEA RegistrationsFunding from the Marijuana IndustryKey DefinitionsConflict of InterestAbout COICOI Case StudiesConflict of Interest Oversight CommitteeFrequently Asked QuestionsStaff DirectoryForms & ReferencesCOI ProceduresDisclosure ChartOther DisclosuresMaterial Transfer AgreementsResearch GiftsPolicies & GuidanceResearch DisclosuresHuman Subjects Research (IRB)National Science Foundation (NSF) PolicyNon-governmental Sponsor (State Law)Public Health Service (PHS) RegulationsSBIR/STTRUC Discovery GrantDual Use Research of Concern (DURC)Export ControlsAre You An Exporter?Deemed Export Certification (I-129)Economic and Trade Sanctions (OFAC)International Shipping and Hand-CarryingInternational TravelRestricted EntitiesUnannounced Site Visits by Outside Investigating AgenciesControlled ItemsBiological AgentsExport Control BasicsExport Control VideosTraining/EducationFrequently Asked Questions Guidance on Foreign Relationships/AffiliationsImportance of Export Control CompliancePenaltiesRegulatory Exemptions and ExclusionsTechnology Transfer/Research TermsWho To ContactResearch Protections
+
Animal Care & UseApplications & FormsConducting ResearchContact UsProtocol Writing Tips & GuidanceResearch Policies & GuidanceRMS User GuideSubmit to the IACUCTraining & Education
+
Human Research ProtectionsAbout HRP and the IRBStaff DirectoryIRB MembersOther UCI CommitteesParticipantsResearchersEducation and Quality Improvement Program (EQUIP)Single IRB (sIRB) / ReliancesReliance Agreement Table
+
Human Stem Cell ResearchActivities that Require hSCRO ReviewCell Line Provenance GuidanceCharge of the UCI hSCROEthical Guidelines, Regulations and StatutesHow to Submit Protocols to the UCI hSCROModifications to Approved ResearchOther UCI Reviews for Stem Cell ResearchStem Cell ResourcesUCI hSCRO Frequently Asked QuestionsInstitutional BiosafetySponsored ProjectsAboutSponsored Projects Departmental AssignmentSponsored Projects Staff ListingApplications & FormsClinical TrialsClinical Trial Budget ConsiderationsConfidential Disclosure AgreementsLaunching and Conducting the TrialMaster AgreementsNegotiation of Clinical Trial AgreementsThe Starting PointContracts & Grants AdministrationCloseoutGetting StartedInstitutional InformationResponsibility MatrixGift vs. GrantPost-award AdministrationPre-Award AdministrationProposal PreparationState of California GuidanceSubawardsForms & ReferencesSubaward Initiation and SetupSubaward ManagementSubawards During Proposal PreparationGift vs. GrantInstitutional InformationPolicies & ProceduresRates & FeesClinical Research Finance Assessment (CRFA)Employee Fringe BenefitsFacilities and Administrative (F&A) Cost RatesGraduate Student Fees and Tuition RemissionInstitute for Clinical Translational ScienceServices and ResourcesIRB Fees for Clinical Trials with For-Profit SponsorsNIH/SAMHSA/AHRQ Salary Rate Caps by Federal Fiscal YearTraining & EducationTraining & EducationAnimal Care & Use TrainingExport Controls TrainingHuman Research Protections TrainingIntegrity in Research TrainingSponsored Projects Training
Privacy and Legal NoticePrivacy and Legal Notice
The University of California, Irvine Office of Research is
committed to protecting the privacy and accuracy of your personally
identifiable information to the extent possible, subject to provisions
of state and federal law. Other than as required by laws that guarantee
public access to certain types of information, or in response to
subpoenas or other legal instruments that authorize disclosure,
personally identifiable information is not disclosed without your
consent.
Information Collection and Use
Categories of personally identifiable information collected by Web
pages managed or maintained by Office of Research at the University of
California, Irvine or by other entities affiliated with the University
of California, Irvine, may include: your Internet location (Internet
domain and IP address), type of browser and operating system used to
access our site, date and time our site was visited, pages visited on
our site, search terms used on our search engines, along with
information you use to fill out forms such as: name, email address,
address, birthday, faculty/staff/student ID number, social security number and ucinetid. This personally identifiable information is predominently used in the processing of research administraition-specific applications, but it may also be
used to respond to user inquiries. Article IX, Section 9 of the
California Constitution grants authority to the University of California
to maintain this information.
Information submitted through online forms and applications on the Office of Research site will be used in a manner described in the instructions provided with each form.
Additionally, the Web server collects, at least temporarily, the
following information: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being
used; Web pages requested; referring Web page; browser used; date and
time. This information is collected to monitor your navigation of our
Web pages. We may use browser-IP-address information and
anonymous-browser history to report information about site accesses and
for profiling purposes. This information is generally used to improve
Web presentation and utilization. We also may use IP address information
for troubleshooting purposes.
These Web pages may use “cookies” in order to deliver Web content
specific to individual’s Web navigation interests or to keep track of
online transactions.
Disclosure of Collected Information
The University of California, Irvine Office of Research will not
disclose or share, without your consent, personally identifiable
information, except for certain explicit circumstances in which
disclosure may be required by law. Nor will the
University of California, Irvine Office of Research distribute or sell your personally
identifiable information to third-party organizations.
Policy Changes
This privacy policy has been created and approved by the University of California, Irvine Office of Research. Any revisions to this
privacy policy will be posted at this URL. You may submit inquiries
about this policy to or-web-support@uci.edu.
Links to Other Sites
You may encounter links to Web pages of entities not managed or
maintained by the University of California, Irvine Office of Reearch. Those Web pages may have privacy policies that differ from this
one. You also may encounter links to Web sites of organizations not
directly affiliated with the University of California, Irvine. Please be
aware that the University of California, Irvine is not responsible for
the information practices of external organizations. We recommend you
review the privacy statements of each Web page that collects personal
information.
University of California, Irvine Office of Research141 Innovation Drive, Suite 250Irvine, CA 92697
University of California, Irvine Office of Research141 Innovation Drive, Suite 250Irvine, CA 92697
© 2016 The Regents of the University of California      Privacy & Legal Notice
University of California, Irvine Office of Research141 Innovation Drive, Suite 250Irvine, CA 92697
© 2019 The Regents of the University of California      Privacy & Legal Notice
